Wow!
That's great!
Thank you so much for your hard work.
Thank you so much for your hard work!
I took a video of you dancing!
The highlight is these dowdy shoes!
Dowdy shoes?
Since I came all the way to Tokyo
I thought I'd go see the Budokan.
Aaaaahhh...
Let's go see the Budokan!
I'm in Akasaka right now.
I'm in Akasaka, but the Budokan is on the road to Budokan
I think I'll go outside.
Congratulations!
Today? Today?
How's everybody doing today? Today?
How long is today? Are we going to walk out there?
Let's go! Let's go!
You're walking!
They're going the other way.
Yeah!
Bye-bye!
Gobble!
Wow!
You know, the other day, Yamada-san, we were at the battlefield.
It's too early, I'll go a little slower.
Have you guys been to Budokan?
Yes!
I went to Judge Monkey's breakup live!
Oh, wow!
I fought a monkey in a previous life.
Yeah!
Monkey Monkey!
I'm going to be an eggplant.
Whoa!
what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what.
They say you have to put the booby on to get it started.
Yay, they're wearing green in Sendai, too!
I think people in Tohoku have an image of green Tokyo, but there's also a lot of green in Marie, but so is Tokyo!
Who's Tokyo? The Emperor lives here!
It's amazing! It's so moving!
We're on our way to the Budokan. Let's say what we want to say at the Budokan.
I've been saying this for a while... there will be 48 parents and relatives from Tohoku.
We've got 48 people now, and it's going to be a perfect fit, so I want the Tohoku 48 to dance with the parents.
Great! Can we ride on a wagon?
The trolley? Can't we ride?
I'm sure it's possible. But it's more like an arena. I've always wanted to ride on one.
Yeah, I know how you feel. I'd love to.
Roller skating? Oh, yeah.
There's nothing I can't do.
I forgot. Out!
Guess it was too soon.
Wow, great youth balloon.
Gesso.
Today, we got in the Hiace with our suitcases on board.
As soon as we arrived
I danced for an hour and a half in the lesson hall.
And then, oh no! Time! Time! And then I said, "Time!
I rushed out, grabbed my luggage and got out.
I'm walking now.
I'm not an ogre for planning, but I am an ogre for today's schedule.
Nice smile, Chamin!
Haru-chan got her hair cut today.
Ah, yes.
I've never seen it before.
It's a freshly cut moisturizer
It's shorter than I thought it would be
Maru-chan hair
Oh, go away!
Bye, bye, bye!
Maybe I'll go to a different world.
Don't go to another world.
There you go!
Oh, he's back.
I'm clean.
You're clean.
He's clean.
Meet me at this girl's place.
Semper Hall.
Come on.
Sember Hall.
I'm on Deep Coast Road.
Oh!
Yes, yes.
That's all of it.
About a half hour to go.
It's huge.
No, 30 more minutes.
It's true, those are all made of waffles.
Oh, my first time on it.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
Oh, wait.
I don't get it.
Oh, really?
Um...
I'm just...
I'm afraid of slipping.
Um...
I was doing it in a place where the camera couldn't hear me.
I'm seriously the one who ends up blabbering to myself the whole time.
Oh, my God.
Check once.
Check with Yuna.
It's delicious.
It's good.
If it looks funny...
But Yuna laughs at everything.
That's for sure.
Yes, I'm sure.
Looks good in the water.
Yes, sir.
Yes. - Yes.
Yes. Yes.
Hydrofluid
Yes
I can't wait to eat and walk around.
Yes.
I want the world to be a better place.
I hope so.
What will you eat when you get there?
First thing.
Uh...
Squid.
Squid?
I was surprised that it wasn't as cute as I thought it would be.
Oh, sorry.
What?
I knew it.
I'm an idol.
I don't know.
I don't know why.
Who's the idol?
No, he's not cute.
I don't know...
the other day
Kuhoku Kusun's
Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah.
Ah, yes
Oh, yes
Kuhokusan's
When I looked at the old pictures...
the difference in height is really amazing...
Ah...
I'm not going to Miyashiro shinohun-chan.
I have to go.
I have to go, right?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ah!
You're good.
You're fine.
I was just saying how I'm doing.
We were all still in elementary school and junior high.
I see.
You've grown up so much, haven't you?
Yeah, I really am.
I felt it myself.
Because Paya and Kanen were like this.
Yes, they were tiny.
And Runchan and the others...
Because they were big.
Yeah.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It all happened so fast.
Right?
If you ever go to Udokan...
I wonder if I'll remember this day
Right?
Because it's still here somehow.Because there's something left here.
Hey.
Mr. Road to Talk.
Mr. Tork.
Talk, talk, talk, talk.
Road to Talkan.
No.
Oh!
Whoa!
I see it! I see it!
I can see it!
Don't you wanna see?
Don't you want to see it?
I'm talking about Budokan.
I'm a real hard-on.
And I thought it was Budokan.
Oh, no.
That's not good.
So at Budokan.
When the senior group said they were going to do it at Budokan
I was kind of like, you know, through the Budokan farm.
I had this image of what it would be like.
What kind of live music club?
I don't know.
I didn't think it was the Budokan.
I see.
A little bird.
I don't know...
I'll never get there.
But that's Budokan.
We're not allowed to go through here.
Why can't we go through here?
It's for my birthday party.
Is that so?
Hey...
He's saying something.
Laughing.
Walk.
There it is.
Let's take a walk.
Excuse me.
That's it.
I can't go in there.
I'm sure it's a lot of walking again.
Up this hill.
Surprise!
Like you'd have the guts to go in here.
Is that what you mean?
Laughing.
Wouldn't that be great?
If I watch it now, I'll miss all the fun.
Nice job.
That's a good idea.
It makes me even more excited!
I'll be here the morning of the event, and I'll see you all there.
Oh my god!
I'm so excited to go to our show!
Make sure you all get your lines right!
LOL!
I'm gonna miss this.
Want to hear it?
Let's hear it.
We'll walk in a momma's car?
Let's take the Momma.
Oh, my God.
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great.
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great.
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great.
My foot's gone.
My feet.
Oh, my God.
We've arrived at the Budokan.
Here we go! Here we go!
Yay!
I did my best!
We walked from Akasaka for about an hour.
About 4 or 5 kilometers.
What do you think? What do you think?
Seeing it in person made me want to do it here even more.
I want to do it here.
We all want to stand together.
It's wonderful.
Because of the Olympics, we couldn't go to the back.
I couldn't go all the way to the back because of the Olympics, so my goal was here.
Hirafu.
My guess is that we'll go all the way in and stand on stage
and dance the Tenichi dance in three days.
As you can imagine, that's not going to happen
We all talked about it.
Around here, you're all here to make Athrekail
It's like they're trying to make it disappear.
That's great.
You should try mixing it up there.
Great!
But you know what? I'm sorry.
I don't have that kind of time before the Budokan.
That's for sure.Certainly.
Maybe next time I come back.
I'll probably be on my feet by the time you come back.
I'll come back tomorrow.
That's for sure.
If you come tomorrow
I'm going to keep aiming for the Nippon Budokan.
I'll do my best to make it here.
Thank you all for your continued support.
I look forward to working with you.
Let's go for it!
Oh!